No! No!
No.
Rhea! Rhea! Rhea!
I have a student.
Stein Alberts.
Third year, B.S. Math.
Actually, he’s really good.
So, you're always in front of the stage,
watching the production
from the audience's point of view.
Right?
I am Moriarty.
How did you know we're here?
What kind of question is that, Loki?
As far as I remember,
didn’t someone die because you meddled?
Loki, please, save me.
Stein!
One more thing...
Is this the Q.E.D. Club?
I want you to join the Q.E.D. Club.
The Q.E.D. Club
is the one and only detective club
here in Clark University.
I hope it’s always like this.
We can prevent the tragedy
before it happens.
We can save even more lives.
I knew you would be here.
Luthor?
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm obviously here
to check on my brother.
How’s he holding up?
As you can see, he's not here.
Well, that’s obvious,
but you should be able to tell me that.
I'm well aware, Lorelei,
that the two of you live together
in an apartment
three blocks away from here.
Isn’t that right, Miss Lorelei?
Why don't you just visit him
if you're really that concerned about him?
I could.
But, you know…
I don’t wish to ruin his day.
It seems like the mere sight
of my shadow is...
is enough to upset him,
to send him bollocks.
What more if I checked on him in person?
Fair enough.
It also seems like he’s enjoying himself
with the suspension and all.
He hates going to class, so...
he’s probably grateful
that this is his punishment.
By the way,
how’s the progress...
of the campus police
and the school admin's investigation
on Stein?
On the allegation
that our school’s math prodigy
is a criminal mastermind?
Listen, I’m not really supposed
to share this
since the investigation
is still ongoing...
but…
I guess it’s best that you are informed.
At the moment,
there's not a single shred of evidence
that he is what my brother
claims him to be.
No evidence?
Did the campus police check his phone?
There might be conversations
or transactions there linking him
to the cases happening here at Clark U.
Unfortunately, there’s nothing
in his phone that will incriminate him.
No texts,
no calls,
beside one made by my brother but...
the school’s investigation shows
that Stein was actually Moriarty’s victim.
He was locked
in an abandoned building apparently,
so, he couldn’t join
the math screening competition.
So, I was thinking,
how could he be the mastermind
if he himself was a victim?
Luthor, of course,
that’s what he wants you to think.
That he’s the victim,
but he planned all of this.
He’s trying to trick you all,
so you won’t suspect him!
That’s what you like to think.
That’s what you and Loki want to think.
Even if it’s not true,
even if he is not Moriarty.
No, Luthor. Stein admitted he’s Moriarty.
It came straight from his own mouth!
Oh, yeah?
Where’s the evidence? Did you record it?
Did he just casually pick up
a piece of paper and sign it?
Lorelei, I didn’t come here
just to check on my brother.
The student council
is deciding this Friday
whether this club
should be dissolve or not.
What?
To be perfectly candid,
we’re not exactly on your favor.
What motion is that?
Why is our club suddenly involved?
This issue is between Loki and Stein!
The admin has reasons to believe
that this club is enabling my brother
to pursue wrong leads
and fanciful theories
that may harm one of our prodigies.
The school administration has left us
to decide if you guys stay or not.
You didn’t even do anything
to defend your brother
and the club that means so much to him!
If you think I didn’t do anything
for my brother,
and you think
I didn’t pull strings for him,
he would be in jail a long time ago.
I cannot fix all of his messes.
Please send my regards to him.
Now, if you’ll excuse me.
This can’t be happening.
♪ Shadows. ♪
♪ In the dark are crawling. ♪
♪ Keeping watch and barring your way. ♪
♪ As if the line could not be crossed. ♪
♪ To every scream and every tremor. ♪
♪ These walls remain the only witness. ♪
♪ Every noise is etched in here. ♪
♪ Like fire and ammunition
for your memory. ♪
♪ Heed the warnings. ♪
♪ The threats poised to strike. ♪
♪ For this world ♪
♪ is not what you imagined. ♪
♪ Heed the warnings. ♪
♪ Open up your eyes. ♪
♪ For this world ♪
♪ is not what you imagined. ♪
♪ Heed the warnings. ♪
Loki! What have you done
with my teddy bear?
Correction!
My teddy bear.
No longer yours.
Have you forgotten that you
transferred its ownership to me
after throwing it away?
That’s not the issue here!
Why do you have to hang him?
Hey! Don’t worry.
Don’t worry.
Theodore doesn’t mind.
You should even be proud of him.
He helped me prove
the innocence of a young man
accused of hanging his girlfriend.
He couldn’t have committed the crime
because his height lacks a few inches.
The culprit is someone
who is taller than him,
around 6'3".
Theodore?
Why does his name sound so old?
Teddy bears were named
after US President Theodore Roosevelt.
Yes, I know!
But there are so many names
to choose from.
By the way, Professor Morayta
was asking how you're doing.
Luthor also visited.
He was asking
how you're doing as well, Loki.
And he also has a new update
regarding the Moriarty case.
He said that there's still
no concrete evidence against Stein.
Even after checking his phone,
they found nothing.
And lastly...
he also mentioned to me that...
the student council is planning
to dissolve the Q.E.D. Club.
Aren’t you going to say anything, Loki?
I’ve already given you so many updates.
Moriarty is an able strategist.
The fake abduction...
his phone showing nothing illegal.
Every piece was positioned perfectly
to ensure that not a single crime
would be traced back to him.
We need to secure
an irrefutable piece of evidence,
if we want to bring him back to justice.
So what happens to the Q.E.D. Club?
Why do you seem like you’re not worried
that they might dissolve this?
I’m suspended, Lorelei.
So I can’t do anything
for the club right now.
If the president is unavailable…
the burden to deal with alarming issues
falls to the vice president.
Which happens to be you.
So that’s it? Just like that?
Isn’t the club dear to you?
Don’t you feel even a little regret
that you might lose a place
where you made so many memories?
The club might just be a small room
to most students in Clark U…
but not to you, Loki.
For you it can be more than just a room.
What about your memories with Rhe...
It looks like you still want
to ask me something.
Go ahead.
I’m in a mood to give you answers.
Do you feel good now?
Have you finally released all the anger
you’ve been keeping toward Moriarty?
Strangely...
the feeling’s far from satisfaction.
I should be happy that I got my revenge.
But I’m not.
I feel underwhelmed.
I feel disappointed.
Well...
maybe that’s not what justice
is supposed to feel like.
Lori.
Lori! Lori! What the heck?
Oh, my bangs! What is that?
Why are you messing
with this harmless teddy bear?
Sorry, Tita.
It’s just that Loki messed
with my teddy bear!
Correction.
My teddy bear.
Whoever’s teddy bear this is,
your teddy bear, her teddy bear,
whoever’s teddy bear it is,
can you please put
that teddy bear down already?
I feel bad, and I’m hurt!
What the heck?
Tita, it looks like you’re busy right now.
Yeah, I’m really busy!
But it looks like you’re even busier
finding time to do that!
I’m busy because I need
to have this ceiling fixed.
I was going to give some snacks
to the workers,
and I included you as well.
So, there, have some snacks.
This teddy bear must
be getting hot. Poor thing.
It’s been there for so long, right?
Huh?
By the way, Lorelei,
do you have anything to do
tomorrow after your class?
I think I’m still free tomorrow
after class, Tita.
Why? Do you need something from me?
Nothing. Just asking.
You know me. I like asking questions.
How are you?
I’m fine now.
See? I really like asking questions.
I’ll go ahead. Make sure you eat, okay?
Get well soon, Stein.
I hope you wake up from your coma, Stein,
so you can tell the whole truth.
Justice for Stein!
We can't let this slide.
Sending prayers, Stein. Get well soon.
Oh, right.
If only they truly knew
who the real Stein is.
Loki was right.
You’re a really good strategist.
Is this part of your game
to make Loki look like the bad guy?
You’ve killed so many fellow students.
If Loki doesn't care
whether you live or die,
I do.
I want you to stay alive
so you can pay for what you did.
The Q.E.D. Club will make sure
you can’t escape
the sins you’ve committed.
Remember that, Stein.
Pawn to E6.
Queen to E7.
Checkmate.
Why are you up so early?
I want you to have this.
What am I supposed to do about that?
I have my own laptop anyway.
Yesterday, you seemed
really concerned about our club.
Thus, I’m offering you its salvation.
Do you want me to smash this
in your brother’s face
and the rest of the student council?
Sure.
That’s fun. But just him.
Spare the others.
Kidding aside,
this laptop is a pandora’s box.
Once what’s inside this leaks,
the campus will definitely be in chaos.
But if you’re careful enough
in opening it,
it can make anyone bow to your will.
And if you want to save our club,
all you have to do is log in
and browse some files.
Okay.
There's a password?
It wouldn't be fun
if I tell you right away.
Try deducing it.
Are you serious?
My laptop has a nine-digit code.
When decrypted, those numbers
will reveal the word "detective."
Sounds easy, right?
What’s easy about that?
Well, those who aren't aware of my methods
will have a hard time figuring it out.
I already expected
that there was a possibility
our club would be dissolved,
so I prepared for it.
And this day has finally come!
The salvation of our club...
is now in your hands.
Wow. You’re really serious.
Okay, well...
any clue that might help me out?
You can try…
You can try Mary Had A Little Lamb.
Loki, you're supposed to help me,
yet you're making this harder.
Let’s try 4, 5, 2, 5, 3,
2, 9, 4, 5.
What?
So there’s a limit
for incorrect passwords?
What’s with Loki?
He could’ve just told me.
I can’t just keep guessing anymore.
How would a children’s song
help me encrypt the word "detective"?
Is this data?
When was this composed?
It might not be a date shift cipher.
Okay.
Yes!
Okay. I'm doing this for the club.
I need to speak with the Vice President.
Is he there?
Sorry, miss. We’re in a meeting.
But I can relay your message
to him if you want.
No! I need to speak with him in person.
This is an urgent matter.
But, miss, we’re in a meeting.
You don’t understand. This is important!
- I need to speak with him!
- But...
Is there a problem here?
What’s so urgent that you seek
an audience with us, Ms. Lorelei?
I have an offer that you
and the student council can’t refuse.
I’m Lorelei Rios.
And I’m speaking
on behalf of the Q.E.D. Club.
I know you, Lorelei.
I’m Emeraude Emerson,
the Student Council President.
How can we help you?
I want you to make sure
our club won’t be dissolved.
But that's not something we can control.
We’ll vote tomorrow on whether
your club should still be retained.
We can’t dictate each person’s choice.
That’s why I have an offer,
to make sure
the majority will be unanimous
in not agreeing to dissolve our club.
Okay. Let’s see.
Wait a minute...
These are...
Do you remember Charles Meliton?
The serial blackmailer
that tried to extort money
from one of your fellow
student council officers
in exchange for not leaking
those set of photos?
If you dissolve our club tomorrow,
you can expect those photographs
to be leaked online,
via an anonymous user on social media.
It’ll be a huge scandal if that happens.
You know, Lorelei, it’s kinda funny
that you think that this
is enough for us to bend the knee.
I think you have mistaken us, Lorelei.
I don’t know
if I’m the only one who noticed,
or if you’ve been wondering too,
but with everything
that’s been happening at Clark U...
none of this is making it to the news?
I wonder why.
Maybe a media blackout, perhaps?
In the photos you’re holding,
as you can see,
some Student Council officers
are involved
as well as some members
of the Executive Committee.
And after doing some research,
I found that they actually come
from some pretty influential families.
Can you imagine the damage this would do?
To their families' honor
and to the school's image,
if those photographs
were, say, to be leaked?
It would be massive. You're right.
You know, I can’t believe
that you’re using my brother’s method
to bring us to our knee.
You know that it all hundred percent
screams Loki.
Very well, regarding your offer...
we would have to make sure
that none of the contents
will be leaked to the public.
Can you keep your word?
You have my word, Luthor.
And my word is my bond.
Yeah. You better make sure.
So, do we have a deal?
I just did that!
Okay.
Hello, Loki!
Yeah. Any updates?
They took the bait!
They took my offer.
We made a deal.
They won’t dissolve
the Q.E.D. Club anymore.
Okay.
Huh?
Just okay?
No “good job” or anything?
I was 99.9% certain
they’d accept our offer.
Okay. Fine.
Wait, Lorelei.
Are you free this weekend?
I don’t have anything planned
this weekend yet.
Why?
I’d like to invite you on a date.
Huh? What?
I said, I’d like to invite you on a date.
Come on, Loki. Is this a prank?
Yup!
Okay.
But, seriously, are you really free
this weekend?
An acquaintance needs our help
with a strange case.
And we both owe him a favor,
so he deserves our help.
Wait, in what way do I owe this person?
And I don’t even know
that acquaintance of yours.
Just do it!
You’ll find out this weekend.
Just make sure you’re free this Saturday.
But...
You seem happy.
What do you need, Maggie?
Nothing.
I just heard you made a deal
with the Student Council.
They say you have
some very scandalous files?
Impressive.
Your blackmail is effective.
Though I’m a bit disappointed because
you’re starting to pick up Loki’s schemes.
I expected more from you.
Sorry, but I don’t care
if you’re disappointed in me.
I don’t need to please you.
I still don’t get why you’re still
so invested in the Q.E.D. Club.
Don’t you want a quiet life
and just finish your degree in peace?
And what? Just turn a blind eye
to my dying schoolmates?
I can’t do that, Maggie.
But, yes, you’re right.
I do want a quiet life.
But we can only study in peace,
if we’re safe.
And that’s why I’m with the Q.E.D. Club!
Excuse me.
Hello, Tita Martha?
Hello, Lori!
I know you’re still in class,
I was wondering if you could meet me
at the coffee shop.
It’s next to your school,
Diogenes Coffee Shop.
After your class.
Okay, Tita.
Ah, okay. Let's meet, okay?
Okay. See you there.
Lori.
Tita, what does this mean?
Because...
Come on. Come on. Come on!
Come here. Come here!
Papa?
What are you doing here?
I’m here to pick you up.
You’re going home.
Wait. Wait!
Sit down. Sit down first.
Wait.
Kuya, don’t be so abrupt with Lori.
Maybe you can talk
things through properly.
Thank you, Martha.
Alright.
We haven’t seen each other for months,
and now you suddenly show up
just to send me home?
That’s so...
Tea? Coffee?
Neither.
All I want to know...
is why you’re making me go home
in the middle of the school year.
This is not the first time
you get yourself into trouble.
I thought sending you to your aunt
would straighten you out.
Clearly, I was mistaken.
Loki!
- Stop it! Stop it!
- Fucking bastard!
That's enough! That's enough!
Where did you get this?
That’s not important anymore.
Lori, you’re befriending
violent people like that.
Why are you hanging out with them?
Have you become like that too? Huh?
I’m so disappointed in you.
Anyway, I’m here
to take you back to Manila.
You’ll be studying again
at St. Bartholomew.
- I don’t want to go back there.
- You have nothing to worry about.
Everyone involved in that incident
has been expelled.
Didn’t Al tell you?
Anyway, I know
the board of directors there.
I can have them arrange
a speedy transfer for you.
After you sent me away here,
now you want me to come back?
You can’t just toss me
wherever you want me to be.
Actually, you know what? I can!
If I wanted to, I can drag you
all the way back to Manila.
As long as I’m the one paying
for your education and supporting you,
I can choose where you live
and where you go to school.
Considering everything that’s happened,
it’s probably better
if you stay close to me.
That way, I can watch over you.
I can make sure that this
will never happen again.
You know, Lori, no matter where I put you,
you always end up in trouble.
That’s not true.
Papa, you didn’t even listen to my side.
Papa, I’m not a kid anymore.
I won’t allow you
to control my life again.
You know...
you’re lucky you didn’t get hurt.
Do you even understand that, huh?
You’ve experienced
losing someone you love.
Yes.
I understand that.
But, Papa, I can take care of myself.
The one you saw in the video? Loki?
He’s not violent like that.
He’s not a bad person.
He was just pushed to his limit,
so he snapped.
But I know that doesn’t excuse
what he did.
And now he’s paying for it.
Belive me, I tried to stop him.
Please, Papa.
I don’t want to go back
to St. Bartholomew.
I like it better here at Clark U.
I have friends here,
and I’m needed here, and...
Look, Lori, I know you’re being stubborn.
You know what, you’re right.
You’re of legal age.
You deserve the freedom
to control your own life.
Remember this...
with that freedom comes responsibility.
Okay, let’s do it your way.
For now.
Because if this happens again,
you know what will happen, you understand?
Yes, Papa.
Pa...
It’s been a long day.
I need to get some rest.
Yeah.
By the way, what do you think of Alistair?
Do you think he’s a perfect match for you?
Why is he like that?
We haven’t seen each other in so long,
but it doesn’t seem to matter to him.
I know he cares about me,
but not like a daughter.
More like a piece of property
he checks from time to time.
He even showed up.
He should’ve just texted.
I don't wanna see him anymore.
I wish you were the one here, Mom.
I really miss you.
Fresh garlic?
Fried rice?
Is someone cooking in the unit?
But...
Loki doesn't cook.
Maybe it's Tita Martha?
But why would she be cooking
in our unit?
Jamie?
Good morning, Lorelei!
Did you sleep well?
Loki dear!
You two seem to be getting along.
Wow. It's like a newly live-in couple.
Sorry for the interruption.
I would just like to introduce to you
your newest schoolmate.
A transferee student.
Please, come in and introduce yourself.
Al?
Excuse me. Hi. Al, we need to talk.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Wait, BFF!
I wanted to bring a case to you.
Oh, no.
Ever since Loki has been gone,
we haven't been accepting cases.
Is that so?
But you can tell me.
Welcome. I've been expecting you.
Actually, I'm pleased to finally
meet you face-to-face, Miss Lorelei.
Ever since I watched that video,
I got so much worried about you, Lori.
Loki taught me how to do this
in case something like this happens.
Actually, I feel like
I was really with Loki earlier
with how quick you were able
to decipher that code.
The only difference is
you genuinely care
about the victims and...
you can actually remember their names.
Help!
MkvDrama.net